Finding Aid for the Rudolph H. Kampmeier, A.B., M.D. Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Professional Career and Academic Appointments*
  - (Box 2)
    The Oxford Players in a series of Romantic Masterpieces; The Ivory Door, Hamlet, and Romeo and Juliet, December 24, Tulane Theatre Louisiana
    The Pajama Game, book by George Abbott and Richard Bissell, music and lyrics by Richard Adler and Jerry Ross
    April 25, 1955’ starring John Raitt, Janis Paige and Eddie Foy, Jr.; choreography by Bob Fosse St. James Theatre NY
    March 29-April 7, 1962’ The Circle Theatre N
    Pal Joey starring Andy Williams and Julie Wilson; music by Richard Rodgers, lyrics by Lornz Hart Columbus, Ohio
    Personal Appearance by Lawrence Riley starring Carole Arden, March 3-12, 1949 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    The Philadelphia Story by Philip Barry starring George Hamilton Columbus, Ohio
    Passing Show of 1926, October 24, 1926 Shubert-Detroit Opera Detroit House
    The Play's The Thing, a classic modern comedy by Ferenc Molnar, December 25, 1932 Tulane Theatre New Orleans, LA
    Private Lives by Noel Coward, starring Donald Cook, January 17, 1950 Ryman Autitorium N
    Pygmalion by George Bernard Shaw January 25-February 4, 1950 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Michael Rabin, violinist; 1954-1955 presented by the Community Concert Association [N]
    Radio City Music Hall Program-week beginning Thursday, April 14, 1966; Music Hall Grand Organ RAce with the Wind Glory of Easter Hello Spring Ambassadors of Spring Flowers that Bloom in the Spring Dog Antics Happy Bunnies April in Paris Radio City Music Hall N
    Radio City Music Hall Program cont Handiest Chap this Spring Spring in Eastertown Radio City Music Hall NY
    The Singing Nun’ starring Debbie Reynolds Ricardo Montalban, Greer Garson, Agnes Moorehead, and Chad Everett
    The Rainmaker by N. Richard Nash, January 12- 21, 1956 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    The Red Mill, a comic Operetta, by Victor Herbert, October 15-25, 1952 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Roberta, a play with music in two acts, based on a story by Alice Duer Miller, music by Jerome Kern, May 31-June 10, 1950 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Relative Strangers by Armand Salacrou, March 19-28, 1959 Theatre Nashville N
    Romeo and Juliet, by William Shakespeare, April 26-May 6, 1950 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    The Royal Family or A Comedy of Actors, by George S. Kaufman and Edna Ferber March 15-25, 1950 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    The Royal Hunt of the Sun, a new play by Peter Shaffer, starring Christopher Plummer, Da’id Carradine and George Rose Anta Theatre NY
    The St. Louis Symphony Orchestra, conductor Vladimir Golschmann, January 7, 1954 N
    St. Louis Woman, book by Arna Bontemps and Countee Cullen, May 28-June 7, 1952 Nashville Community N
    San Carlo Grand Opera Company, January 9-12 Municipal Auditorium N
    San Francisco Ballet, April 4, 1960 War Memorial Opera House N
    Say, Darling, a comedy about a musical by Richard Bissell, Abe Burrows, and Marian Bissell, October 7-17, 1959 New Theatre Nashville N
    Second Decade of the Playhouse describing the theatre movement in Nashville, published October 8, 1945 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Seperated Tables by Terence Rattigan, December 5-13, 1958 Theatre Nashville N
    The Seven Year Itch by George Axelrod May 24’June 2, 1956 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    The Silver Whistle by robert E. McEnroe January 16-26, 1952 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    The Spider, a mystery melodrama by Fulton Oursler and Lowell Brentano, October 5-15, 1949 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    The Sound of Music, music and lyrics by Rodgers & Hammerstein, starring Jeannie Carson and John van Dreelen, April 29- May 1, 1963 Ryman Auditorium N
    South Pacific, music and lyrics by Rodgers and Hammerstein, starring Martha Wright and George Britton N
    Rise Stevens of the Metropolitan Opera Association, 1953-54, presented by the Community Concert Association [N]
    The Student Prince in Heildelberg, spectacular operetta, September 28, 1925 Shubert-Lafayette
    Swan Lake, Music by P. I. Tschaikowsky, choreography after Lev Ivanov, October 25, 1963 Tulsa Municipal Tulsa, Oklahoma
    Swan Song by Ben Hecht and Charles MacArthur, October 29-November 5, 1947 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Sweethearts, an operetta in two acts, book by Harry B. Smith and Fred De Gresac, Victor Herbert's production, May 30-June 8, 1949 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    The Taming of the Shrew, by William Shakespeare, starring Alfred Lunt and Lynn Fontanne, January 12, 1940 Ryman Auditorium N
    The Teahouse of the August Moon by John Patrick, starring John Forsythe and Eli Wallach, April 23, 1955 Martin Beck Theatre NY
    The Tempest by William Shakespeare, December 10-20, 1947 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    A Thousand Clowns, starring Van Johnson Gale Gladstone, Doug Chapin, Donald Buka, and Iggie Wolfington, August 30, 1964 Columbus, Ohio
    Time and The Tide, a new play by Paula and Edward Hussey, January 27-February 5, 1949 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Time Out For Ginger by Ronald Alexander November 22-December 1, 1956 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Time Remembered, a romantic comedy by Jean Anouilh, starring Helen Hayes, Richard Burton, and Susan Strasberg, April 28, 1958 Morosco Theatre NY
    Helen Traubel, dramatic Soprano, Metropolitan Opera Association, presented by the Community Concert Association, 1952-53 [N]
    Two Blind Mice, a comedy by Sam Spewack October 17-27, 1951 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    The Two Mrs. Carrolls, an exciting mystery thriller by Martin Vale, January 21-30, 1954 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    The Unsinkable Molly Brown, a new musical comedy, music and lyrics by Meredith Wilson, Book by Richard Morris, June 26, 1961 Winter Garden NY
    Venus At Large by Henry Denker, starring David Wayne, William Prince, Joyce Jameson and Ernest Truex, 1962 Walnut Theatre Philadelphia
    The Voice of The Turtle by John Van Druten October 14-23, 1948 Nashville Community Playhouse N
    Wait a Minim!, a musical entertainment by Leon Gluckman, April 1966 John Golden Theatre NY
    The Women by Clare Booth, December 27, Ryman Auditorium N
    Yellow Jack by Sidney Howard in collaboration with Paul DeKruif, March 25-30, 1935 Le Petit Theatre New Orleans, LA